Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Financial Series, 1975-2007; 1
  - Customer Files subseries, 1975-2007; 1.1
    - East End Food Co-op, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - East-West Books, 1981-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Elliott Bay Books Co., 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Equality Books, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Ernie's Records, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Every Woman's Place, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Excellent Records, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Flipside, 1979-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Jane Fishman Enterprises, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Garbage LP's, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The George St. Co-op, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Gettysburg College Store, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Giant Sound Centers, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Glad Day Bookshop, 1979-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Golden Sheaf Trading Co., 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Good Foods, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Graffiti Records, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Grailville, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Gramophont, 1978; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Grapevine, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Grok Bookstore, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Grove Bookworm, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Half the Sky Bookstore, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Head Over Heels, 1981-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Heads Together, 1981-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Heidi's & Co, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Herizon, 1979-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Herland Bookstore, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Hershelf Bookstore, 1978-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Hi Fi Camera Center, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Highlander, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Hogeye Music, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Hollins College, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Horizon Bookstore, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Horizon Records, 1979-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - A House of Our Own, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - House of Records, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Inside Out, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - It's About Time (Seattle, WA), 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - It's About Time (Lakeworth, FL), 1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Jan Phillips, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Jerritt & Morgan, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Jim's LP, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Joe's #2, 1981-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Kay's Book Studio, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Key LPs, 1981-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Koinonia Partners, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Labrys, 1978-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Left Bank Books, 1978; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Leisure Landing, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Libreria del Pueblo, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Loose Ends, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Lunacy, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Magic Speller Bookstore, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - MacBean's Books & Music, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Marty's Record Shops, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - McCabe's Guitar Shop, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Moby Disc, 1978-1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Modern Times, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Molalla Community Food Store, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Moonstar Teahouse, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Mother's (Virginia Beach, VA), 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Mother's Record & Tape Co (Chesapeake, VA), 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Mother's Record & Tape Co (Hampton, VA), 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Mother's LPs & Tapes (Norfolk, VA), 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Muja Gallery, 1981-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Music Center, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Music City, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Music Loft, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Natalie Lando, 1979-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - New Lifwe Co-op, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - New Earth, 1978-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Claire Noonan, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Northwood Bookstore, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Nostalgia Place Records, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Old Fogey Distributing, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Old Harbor Books, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Old Town Books & LPs, 1983-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - One Way Pub, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Opera House, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Oracle, 1978-1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Our Space, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Paperback, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Paradise Records, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Patchogue-Medford Library, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Pendle Hill Community, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Phoenix Shop, 1986; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Plains Woman, 1977-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Poobah's, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Priarie Dog Recaords, 1980-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Power House, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Radical Information Project Bookstore Collective, 1978-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Radio 437, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rainbow Connection, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rainbow News Ltd, 1982-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rainbow Records, 1981-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Rainbow Place, 1981-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rainbows of Life, 1980-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rather Ripped Records, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Readings Pty. Ltd. (Records & Books), 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Record Corner, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Record Hold, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Record Librarian, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Record Revolution, 1981-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Record Recyler, 1982-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Records Unlimitd, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Recordsphere, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Red Herring Co-op Books, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Red Book, 1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Red Carpet Stereo, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Revolutions, 1975-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Reznick's Inc, 1976-1977; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Ridgetop Records, 1977-1977; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Ripete Records, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rising Woman Books, 1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rhino LPs, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rhyme's LPs, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Robber Joe's Records, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Rock n Road Shop, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - A Room Of One's Own, 1977-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Ruthless, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - E.R. Ruward, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Salt of the Earth, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sam Goody's, 1980-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Schoolkids Records (Columbia, MO), 1978-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Schoolkids (Raleigh, NC), 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Schoolkids Records (Wilmington, NC), 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Semple Street Food Co-op, 1981-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Shameless Hussy, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Shazada's, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Ships Shoes & Sealing Wax, 1981-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Shoreline Woman, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sight and Sound Woman, 1979-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sistermoon, 1977-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sisterspace, 1978-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sister Spirit, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Shipped Disc LP Co-op, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Small Changes Bookstore, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Small Folks Books & Toys, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sojourner Bookstore/Center, 1978; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Soul Shack, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sound Ideas, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sound Odyssey, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sounds Familiar #2, 1978-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Spectrum Books, 1981-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Spinster, 1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Spirit Laden Recoards, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Square Deal, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Stacy's Music Shop, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Stark, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Stephen's, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Stereo Village, 1977; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sweet Emma, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sylph Production, 1981-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Sunrab Book Service, 1983-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - TF International Recoards, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Three Guineas Bookstore, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Tri City Woman's Center, 1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Troubadisc, 1979-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Total Information, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Trivium Books & Gallery, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Tudor Bookshop, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Unicorn Bookcenter, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Unicorn Music Works, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Vaughn's Bookstore, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Vermont Book Shop, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - War Resisters League, 1978-1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Washington & Lee University Record Store, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Whole Note Music Center, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Wilkie News Inc, 1982-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Wizards, 1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Woman to Woman, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womankind Books (Nashville, TN), 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womankind Books & LPs (Santa Barbara, CA), 1978-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womankind Books (Huntington, NY), 1981-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Woman's Books Connection, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womansplace Bookstore, 1979-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - A Woman's Room, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womansound, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womanspace (Ann Arbor, MI), 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womanspace/Diane Hampton (Mobile, AL), 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Woman's Eye, 1979-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Woman's Music Archives, 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - The Woman's Store, 1978-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Woman's Work Bookstore, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Wonderland, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Woolies, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Yes! Bookshop, 1981-1983; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Everywoman's Books, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Frauenbuch-Laden (Koln, Germany), 1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Frauenbuchladen (Hamburg, Germany), 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Frauenbuchvertrie?, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Kobenhauns Bogcafe, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Levande Kuinnor c/o Franane Mirro, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Lilith Frauenbuchladen, 1979-1986; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Lilith's ?, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Vrouwenboekhandel Caf?, 1979; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Woman's Voice, 1978-1982; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Womansline Books, 1986; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - A Woman's Place, 1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Women's Book, Gift, and Music Center, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Xantippe-Frauenbuchhandel, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Backroads Distributors, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Earth Wisdom Music, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Genevieve Productions, 1980-1987; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Global Pacific, 1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Horizon/Women's Music Distribution Company, 1979-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Mill City Music Distribution, 1983-1985; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Paradigm, 1984; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Woman's Music Epxress, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 13)
    - Toronto's Women's Express, 1978-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Touchstone Gallery, 1998; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Tower Gallery, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Town and Campus Records, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Triple Goddess, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Tristate Coalition, 2000; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Tudor Book Shop Ltd., 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Twist and Shout Records, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Lavender Dragon/Two Sisters Bookshop, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Two Sister Trading, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - University of Maryland Barnes & Nobles, 2000; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Under One Roof Books, 1998-2000; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Unitarian Church, 1998; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Unique on Central, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - University of Wisconsin-Madison Memorial Library Acquisitions, 2003; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - York Universities Libraries, 1997; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Western Washington University, 1998; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - University of Wisconsin-Whitewater Library Acquisitions, 1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Upstairs Gallery, 1995-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - First Unitarian Universalist Church of Columbus, 1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Utah State University, 1997; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Valley Books and Gifts, 1997; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Valley Media, Inc./Valley Record Distributors (5 folders), 1994-2005; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Value Music Concepts, 2004; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - VCS Community Change Project, 1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Venice-Ocean Park Food Co, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Venus Rising, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Mysterious Women/Verlag & Versandbuchhandel, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Vibrant Life Foundation, 2000; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Bottom-Z-Up/Violets and Rainbows, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Volumes and Pleasure, 1992-2000; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Vortex Crystal & Gem, 1991-2000; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Walking Through Walls, 1997; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Walsh Homeopathic, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Wandering Moon, 2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Whidney Cybercafe and Book Store/Warm Wind Books, 1988-1999; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Washington National Cathedral, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Waterloo Music Company Limited, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Watertown Unified School District, 1998; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Water Tower Books, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Wax Trax, 1993-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - Webster University Library, 2005; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - We Think The World Of You, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - WGBH Radio, 1998; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - White Rabbit, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 14)
    - White Rabbit (2 folders), 1984-1998 (Box 15)
    - White Swan Music Inc., 1995-2004; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - White Light Specialities & Import, 1998; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Whistling Women, 1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Wicca, 1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Wild Things, 1993-2000; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Windfall Enterprises, 1997; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - The Winged One, 1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Wise Woman's Herbs (2 folders), 1990-2002 (Box 15)
    - Wise Ways, 1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Witches Brew, 2000; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Dorothy Abbott for WMNF Radio, 1990-1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Woman of Wands, 1991-2000; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Women and Children First (2 folders), 1981-2002 (Box 15)
    - Womancrafts (Provincetown, MA), 1978-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Womancraft (Chapel Hill, NC), 1991-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - The Women's Bookstop, 1998-2000; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Women's Community Library, 1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - The Woman's Perogative, 1993-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Wonderworks, 1990-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Woods and Strings, 2000; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Women of Wisdom Foundation, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Word Is Out Women's Books, 1994-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Words & Spirit, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - World Junkets, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Wort, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Wovoka Trading Co., 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - WPRM, 1994-2003; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Yukon Willie and Jake, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Yvettes Cassettes Didi's, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Hartford Regioon YWCA, 1998; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Zango Music, 1995-2003; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Zebra'Z.com, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 15)
    - Durham County Library, 1990-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - El Dorado Union High School District, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Emery-Pratt Company, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - The Evergreeen State College Jewish Cultural Center, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Fruitport Community Schools, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - SUNY Oswego Student Association, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Glastonbury Board of Education, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Grinnell College Library, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Guilford College Library, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Lafayette College Williams Center for the Arts, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Lamar University-Orange, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Augsburg College Library, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Andrews Library, College of Wooster, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Atkins Library, UNC Charlotte, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Burlingame Public Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Chester County Library and District Center, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Cook Memorial Public Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Cowles Library, Drake University, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Elmhurst Public Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Ella M. Everhard Public Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Greenfield Public Library, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - McCain Library/Acquisitions, Agnes Scott College, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Onondaga County Public Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Ouachita Parish Public Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Princeton University Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Redwood falls Public Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Simons' Rock College Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Stark County District Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Toledo-Lucas County Public Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - The Urbana Free Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Wheelock College Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - King County Library System, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Oxnard Public Library, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Worcester County Library, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - King County Library System, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Kewaunee Public Library, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Walled Lake City Library, 1997; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - The College of St. Catherine, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - The Library of Congress, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Decatur Public Library, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Downers Grove Public Library, 1990-1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Elizabeth Public Library--Music, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Erie Community College Library, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Euclid Public Library, 1990-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Evansville Public Library, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Fort Worth Public Library, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Frank J. Basloe Library, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Greene County Public Library, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Hackettstown Public Library, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Haywood County Public Library, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Indianapolis Marion County Public Library, 1990-1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Idaho Falls Public Library, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Iowa City Public Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Lexington Public Library, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Linwood Public Library, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Lincoln City Libraries, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Los Angeles Public Library, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Madison Public Library, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Memphis Public Library, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Mills Music Library, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Missoula Public Library, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Multnomah County Library, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - D.H. Hill Library--NCSU, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Neill Public Library, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Newton Public LIbrary, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Northeastern University Library, 1992-1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - The New York Public Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Conservatory Library, Oberlin College, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Ocean County Library, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Port Townsend Public Library, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Libreria La Tertulia, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Riverside City & County Library, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Rockford Public Library, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Santa Clara Public Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Sanibel Public Library, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - San Francisco Public Library, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Skokie Public Library, 1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Salt Lake City Library, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - St. Louis County Library, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Sun Prairie Public Library, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Thomas Nelson Community College Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Tulsa City-County Library, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Warren Hunting Smith Library, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Town of Watertown, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Wichita Public Library, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - William Patterson College Library, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Worcester County Library, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Public Library of Cincinnati, 1988-1996; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Dayton & Montgomery County Public Library, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Defiance Public Library, 1989; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Dabney Lancaster Library, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Evansville-Vanderburgh County Public Library, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Lincoln Public Libraries, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - East Meadow Public Library, 1989; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Seattle Public Library, 1989; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Schaumberg Township District Library, 1989-1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Louisville Public Library, 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Manhasset High School, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Mankato State University, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Margery Waggod, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Minneapolis College of Art & Design, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Maine State Library, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Martha's Vineyard Regional High School, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Maryview Hospital, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Meredith College, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Middlebury College Music Library, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Middleton Public Library, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Modesto City Schools, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Monroe County Public Library, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Monroe Communtiy College, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Montclair State University, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Montgomery College Library, 1989; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Mount Vernon Center for Community Mental Health, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Muskingum College, 1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - NARAL NC, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Neumann College Library, 1990-1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Northern Michigan University, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - North Shore Community College, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Oneida Indian Nation, 1995; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Oakton Community College, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Ohio State University at Lima, 1990; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Old Dominion University Bookstore, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Orange County Sheriff, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Portland State University, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Punahou School, 1994; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Gail Polivy, 1993; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Paramount Unified School District, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)
    - Patagonia Public Library, 1991; 1 folders (Box 16)